http://www.discountdance.com/privacy

Privacy Policy of www.discountdance.com
This Website collects some Personal Data from its Users.
Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
Advertising
Microsoft Advertising, Facebook Lookalike Audience, Google AdSense, Google Ad Manager and Google Ads Similar audiences
Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data
Facebook Audience Network
Personal Data: Cookies; unique device identifiers for advertising (Google Advertiser ID or IDFA, for example); Usage Data
Direct marketing via SMS
Personal Data: first name; last name; phone number
Analytics
Google Analytics, Google Ads conversion tracking, Facebook Ads conversion tracking (Facebook pixel) and Mouseflow
Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data
Contacting the User
Integration of Freshsales with Freshchat and/or Freshdesk
Personal Data: email address; first name; geography/region; last name; phone number
Phone contact
Personal Data: phone number
Contact form
Personal Data: address; city; email address; first name; last name
Mailing list or newsletter
Personal Data: Cookies; date of birth; email address; first name
Displaying content from external platforms
Google Fonts
Personal Data: Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
YouTube video widget and Google Maps widget
Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data
Handling payments
PayPal, Amazon Payments and WorldPay
Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
Infrastructure monitoring
New Relic
Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
Interaction with external social networks and platforms
Facebook Like button and social widgets and Pinterest “Pin it” button and social widgets
Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data
Managing support and contact requests
Freshdesk
Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
Remarketing and behavioral targeting
Facebook Custom Audience
Personal Data: Cookies; email address
Facebook Remarketing, Google Ad Manager Audience Extension and Google Ads Remarketing
Personal Data: Cookies; Usage Data
Traffic optimization and distribution
Cloudflare
Personal Data: Cookies; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
Further information about Personal Data
Selling goods and services online
The Personal Data collected are used to provide the User with services or to sell goods, including payment and possible delivery.
The Personal Data collected to complete the payment may include the credit card, the bank account used for the transfer, or any other means of payment envisaged. The kind of Data collected by this Website depends on the payment system used.
Contact information
Owner and Data Controller
Discount Dance LLC
22840 Savi Ranch Parkway
Yorba Linda, CA 92887
Toll Free: (800) 328-7107
Owner contact email: cs@discountdance.com
Latest update: July 01, 2020
iubenda hosts this content and only collects the Personal Data strictly necessary for it to be provided.
Show the complete Privacy Policy
